{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii decimal code for the uppercase letter ‘A’?",
        "options": [
          "74",
          "65",
          "90",
          "66"
        ],
        "answer": "65"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ASCII code for the letter 'P'?",
        "options": [
          "77",
          "78",
          "79",
          "80"
        ],
        "answer": "80"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the lowercase letter ‘q’?",
        "options": [
          "115",
          "120",
          "113",
          "178"
        ],
        "answer": "113"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the value for the letter ‘C’?",
        "options": [
          "67",
          "27",
          "97",
          "77"
        ],
        "answer": "67"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code corresponds to the letter ‘D’?",
        "options": [
          "25",
          "78",
          "69",
          "68"
        ],
        "answer": "68"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter ‘j’?",
        "options": [
          "106",
          "107",
          "108",
          "109"
        ],
        "answer": "106"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii value for the letter ‘Q’?",
        "options": [
          "113",
          "81",
          "34",
          "119"
        ],
        "answer": "81"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter ‘t’?",
        "options": [
          "120",
          "116",
          "150",
          "112"
        ],
        "answer": "116"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code represents the digit ‘2’?",
        "options": [
          "40",
          "50",
          "60",
          "70"
        ],
        "answer": "50"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code stands for the digit ‘9’?",
        "options": [
          "97",
          "54",
          "57",
          "21"
        ],
        "answer": "57"
      },
      {
        "question": "What decimal ascii code represents the symbol ‘&’?",
        "options": [
          "49",
          "38",
          "88",
          "97"
        ],
        "answer": "38"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code corresponds to the symbol ‘%’?",
        "options": [
          "37",
          "27",
          "85",
          "77"
        ],
        "answer": "37"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii value for the symbol ‘$’?",
        "options": [
          "36",
          "37",
          "38",
          "39"
        ],
        "answer": "36"
      },
      {
        "question": "What ascii code for the symbol ‘@’?",
        "options": [
          "88",
          "99",
          "64",
          "56"
        ],
        "answer": "64"
      },
      {
        "question": "What decimal ascii code represents the digit ‘7’?",
        "options": [
          "55",
          "56",
          "57",
          "58"
        ],
        "answer": "55"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii value for the symbol ‘+’?",
        "options": [
          "44",
          "43",
          "38",
          "22"
        ],
        "answer": "43"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code represents the symbol ‘,’?",
        "options": [
          "44",
          "45",
          "46",
          "47"
        ],
        "answer": "44"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code corresponds to the symbol ‘*’?",
        "options": [
          "43",
          "42",
          "41",
          "44"
        ],
        "answer": "42"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which decimal ascii code represents the symbol ‘?’?",
        "options": [
          "63",
          "65",
          "62",
          "60"
        ],
        "answer": "63"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code represents the symbol ‘/’?",
        "options": [
          "49",
          "47",
          "50",
          "67"
        ],
        "answer": "47"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code correspond to the letter ‘s’?",
        "options": [
          "112",
          "76",
          "109",
          "115"
        ],
        "answer": "115"
      },
      {
        "question": "What character represents ascii code letter ‘W’?",
        "options": [
          "84",
          "87",
          "88",
          "79"
        ],
        "answer": "87"
      },
      {
        "question": "What decimal ascii code represents the digit ‘5’?",
        "options": [
          "60",
          "55",
          "53",
          "48"
        ],
        "answer": "53"
      },
      {
        "question": "What decimal ascii code represents the digit ‘0’?",
        "options": [
          "49",
          "48",
          "50",
          "62"
        ],
        "answer": "48"
      },
      {
        "question": "What character does the ascii code correspond to the letter ‘Z’?",
        "options": [
          "89",
          "90",
          "91",
          "91"
        ],
        "answer": "90"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which character ascii code represents the ‘m’?",
        "options": [
          "110",
          "108",
          "109",
          "120"
        ],
        "answer": "109"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ascii code corresponds to the letter ‘d’?",
        "options": [
          "19",
          "97",
          "99",
          "89"
        ],
        "answer": "97"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘;’?",
        "options": [
          "58",
          "59",
          "60",
          "61"
        ],
        "answer": "59"
      },
      {
        "question": "What ascii code corresponds to the number ‘3’?",
        "options": [
          "50",
          "40",
          "41",
          "51"
        ],
        "answer": "51"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the letter ‘J’?",
        "options": [
          "64",
          "74",
          "84",
          "94"
        ],
        "answer": "74"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the letter ‘H’?",
        "options": [
          "1001001",
          "01010000",
          "10010000",
          "01001000"
        ],
        "answer": "01001000"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the digit ‘3’?",
        "options": [
          "1100011",
          "00110011",
          "100011",
          "011001"
        ],
        "answer": "00110011"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the character represented by ascii code ‘V’?",
        "options": [
          "1001010",
          "00100101",
          "01010110",
          "1010110"
        ],
        "answer": "01010110"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘~’?",
        "options": [
          "10110101",
          "01111110",
          "10000100",
          "01010111"
        ],
        "answer": "01111110"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘@’?",
        "options": [
          "01100010",
          "00111100",
          "01000000",
          "10100000"
        ],
        "answer": "01000000"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the letter ‘U’?",
        "options": [
          "01010101",
          "01110101",
          "11010101",
          "0110101"
        ],
        "answer": "01010101"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the digit ‘4’?",
        "options": [
          "00100100",
          "1100100",
          "0110100",
          "1000100"
        ],
        "answer": "0110100"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘)’?",
        "options": [
          "0101000",
          "10010101",
          "00101010",
          "01011001"
        ],
        "answer": "01011001"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code character of ‘X’?",
        "options": [
          "0101101",
          "1011000",
          "10010101",
          "01011000"
        ],
        "answer": "01011000"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code symbol of ‘+’?",
        "options": [
          "0101011",
          "11010101",
          "10100000",
          "00101011"
        ],
        "answer": "00101011"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘$’?",
        "options": [
          "1001000",
          "1101001",
          "01000011",
          "00100100"
        ],
        "answer": "00100100"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the letter ‘z’?",
        "options": [
          "1100110",
          "01011010",
          "1100101",
          "00111010"
        ],
        "answer": "01011010"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the letter ‘A’?",
        "options": [
          "1000001",
          "01000001",
          "1100001",
          "00100001"
        ],
        "answer": "01000001"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the digit ‘5’?",
        "options": [
          "01000101",
          "1100101",
          "00110101",
          "1000101"
        ],
        "answer": "00110101"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol ‘#’?",
        "options": [
          "00100011",
          "01000011",
          "01110000",
          "1100011"
        ],
        "answer": "00100011"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol of ‘space’?",
        "options": [
          "01101100",
          "00101001",
          "00100000",
          "00111011"
        ],
        "answer": "00100000"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the ascii code for the symbol of ‘:’?",
        "options": [
          "00111010",
          "00101100",
          "01110000",
          "01110001"
        ],
        "answer": "00111010"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which binary code represents the ASCII character 'F'?",
        "options": [
          "01000110",
          "10000110",
          "11000110",
          "00100010"
        ],
        "answer": "01000110"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following binary sequences corresponds to the ASCII character '3'?",
        "options": [
          "10000110",
          "01100011",
          "00110011",
          "11110011"
        ],
        "answer": "00110011"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is the binary representation of the ASCII character '5'?",
        "options": [
          "01100101",
          "01010000",
          "00110101",
          "10101010"
        ],
        "answer": "00110101"
      }
    ]
  }
  